As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled!
La la la la la!
Yeah yeah yeah!
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure.
We're itching to try!
Get ready to roam!
So all aboard now we're said to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep!
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun!
All this excitement is second to none!
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled!
La la la la la!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared.
As long as I keep that feeling there!
With that, let us keep up the pace!
While enjoying every
trip from place to place!
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained!
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride!
Laughing out when they are found!
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous!
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mass.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
The doctor home?
What if no one lives here?
Beats the zombies.
I say we give it a look.
The lights just turned on.
That's a good sign, right?
But why would they shine a
spotlight on this old well?
It's weird.
Welcome. Welcome.
One, two, three.
And four, five
This crazy woman is throwing plates!
Six, seven Why are you only attacking me?
Why, you ask?
Because you alone are not
allowed to enter the mansion?
You two are just fine, though.
Uh, I'm confused?
Now you, get out!
Eight, nine.
I don't get it!
Stop it, that's enough! What?
Please nothing scary.
Eh hope he doesn't throw plates?
We can make an exception just
this once, can't we, Shandora?
Forgive me if we startled you.
You must excuse her, you see.
She was once engaged to a wealthy man.
But to test his love, she shot her
templates from his cherished dining set.
Sadly, he then called off the engagement.
Cast out of her home in disgrace.
She has become my personal servant
with a boundless plate grudge.
Yeah, I don't really care.
And as you may have already surmised, I
am the long-missing world-famous surgeon,
Dr. Hawkback.
A genius in the eyes of
many. Fool! Ted! Usopp!
Hey, Shandora!
We went over this.
I said he could come inside.
When you don't listen to me, then I
look like a fool in front of our guests.
I wish every last plate in
this world would disappear.
I got it!
You don't have to tell me!
I mean, I just got done
explaining it, didn't I?
Chopper, that's who
you were talking about?
Dr.
Hogback, it's really him!
Doesn't look like a genius to me.
Shut up, Nami!
I'll make an exception this once.
All three of you may enter.
We'll continue our conversation inside.
Follow me.
Uh, there you have it.
Please make yourselves a joke.
I still don't get why she
hated me so much, but whatever.
I guess at least we get to go in now.
Right.
Anything's better than that creepy forest.
Oh, uh, hey, wait.
I'm still here.
It's quite rare for me to receive
guests, but my, you certainly are filthy.
Was it a stressful trip?
Well, yes, but it's sort
of a long story. We, uh...
Go ahead, Nami.
I can talk to him about
doctor stuff later.
We were attacked by a bunch
of zombies in the forest?
So we ran away and came
here to take shelter.
Zombies, huh?
We also saw a bunch of crazy
monsters that were straight out
of a horror story What the heck
is up with this creepy island?
I mean, you live here, right?
You gotta know something So these
beasts were chasing you, were they?
And yet you still made
it here in one piece.
Quite impressive!
But to answer your question.
I don't know much about
those creatures either.
Which is precisely why I'm here?
Oh, you mean you're studying zombies?
It's a brand new realm of medical research
Yes, indeed.
Although most people
associate zombies with fear,
what if you think of them in terms of
someone who has come back from the dead?
Then it's a miracle!
The dream of all doctors!
Everyone in this world has a loved one
they'd like to see come back to life.
Why, that's human nature.
And yet the medical community condemns it.
Madness, they call it.
I'm trying to blame God, they say.
That's why I disappeared from society,
so I could continue my research in seclusion
on this island without interruption.
Oh, wow.
So I finally found out the truth.
But just think, if your
research here is a success,
then you're going to bring happiness to
thousands of people all over the world.
As a doctor myself, sir,
I'm behind you all the way.
How open-minded.
Why, thank you, Dr. Chopper.
Even if you acknowledge me as a doctor,
you won't get on my good
side, you big dummy.
Could I have your autograph?
Oh, of course.
to my dear Dr. Chopper.
So do you think you could give me
a little tour of your lab later?
No one, and I mean no one,
can look inside my lab.
Ah!
Come on here, Century!
Can't you at least put
the flan on a plate?
Is that too much to ask?
I wish every last plate in
this world would disappear.
Well, this sort of thing
does tend to happen,
so rest assured, I'm always quite adamant
about keeping the tablecloth clean.
Okay, I'll eat then.
You could still use a spoon, you idiot!
It's so sweet, I love it!
I've prepared a bath for you.
Since you're all filthy, you should
take one before you go to bed.
I almost forgot to ask you.
There's someone else who came
to this island before us.
This may sound crazy, but have you
seen a skeleton roaming around today?
A skeleton?
Yeah, he had an afro and he was in
a really good mood for a dead guy.
Course,
even for this place,
I know it'd still be weird to see a
skeleton walking around and talking.
So you're sure he didn't come by?
Never seen him.
All right, then.
It's no big deal.
Is it really him?
No, it couldn't be.
I know I shouldn't, but
I want to take a peek.
What? You do?
Chopper, I'm shocked.
I'm not talking about Nami's
butt, you silly human.
The thing I want to take a peek at is Dr.
Hogback's awesome laboratory.
Speak for yourself.
It's probably haunted.
Why do we have to sit out here?
You know, Nami, if you're that afraid
to take a shower by your lonesome,
Maybe you should skip it all together.
Maybe some of us don't want to smell
like zombies any longer than we have to.
Stinky butts.
Oh, yeah?
How would you know what
our butts smell like?
Yeah!
As soon as nighttime
hits, we're out of here.
What?
At night?
But it's scary enough during the day!
We finally found a place where
nobody's trying to eat us,
but as soon as we step outside,
we're the main course
in a Straw Hat buffet!
That sounds painful, so for the time
being, I'm staying right where I am,
all we gotta do is wait
for Luffy to show up.
He'll save us.
I think He's right, mommy.
This island's way too creepy for us.
I'm not going through
that graveyard again.
We're not any safer inside than out.
You did take a look at
this mansion, didn't you?
If my hunch about this place is correct,
we are right in the
middle of spook central.
There are more zombies in this
mansion than you can shake a stick at.
Get me out of here!
I need my brains.
The one I'm worried about is Dr.
Hogback himself he's lying to us there's
no doubt about it if he really has Nothing
to do with the zombies on this island then
you tell me why they
leave his place alone?
And terrorize everything else.
Hey, what do you think
we should do, Chopper?
If what she's saying.
is true no way is she saying that Dr.
Hogback is working with the zombies that's
why we're gonna make our escape while
we still have the chance when I'm finished
here we make a break For the coast.
You are a very observant woman.
What?
Usopp, Chopper, what did you say?
We didn't say anything.
But my butt just did.
Maybe you should call me Pusopp.
What the hell is going on?
There isn't anybody in here, is there?
No way.
You're even prettier than
the last on the ship.
Fear looks so good on you. Who said that?
Who's up, Chopper?
Hush, my darling.
Or should I say, my bride.
Did you just now call for us?
I bet you could smell his
fight in here too, huh?
Thank you very much.
Why are you thanking her?
Ah, damn them.
Help me, you idiot!
What are you waiting for?
Save me already!
Something's in here!
Yeah, I can smell it.
Sorry, jeez.
I'm not talking about
your fire, it's a person!
Do something!
He's escaping out the window!
Great, now I have to shoot
at an invisible target?
Special attack, gunpowder, star!
But he must have escaped.
Well, whoever it was, they heard it all.
Wait, who heard what?
I still don't understand all this.
You sure it wasn't my fart?
He was in here the entire time.
An invisible man.
Well, this is no good.
Thanks to this gigantic spider
web, we're dead in the water.
Uh, no pun intended.
Even if meeting that skeleton was a fluke,
the fact that the Thousand
Sunny and the Mini Mary both got
tangled up in this web in the exact
same spot is pretty damn fishy.
Somebody went to a hell
of a lot of trouble
to make sure that when
we enter this place,
it's through the front
gate and nowhere else.
Jeez,
if they were going to
make it that obvious,
they might as well have laid
out a welcome mat for us.
Nero, what are you
mumbling about up there?
You're going to miss all the fun.
Are you seriously about to walk
into a trap that's so damn obvious?
One even a headless zombie would
have the sense to run away from?
Pretty much, yeah!
It's not like we have anything
better to do right now.
It'll be fun!
If you don't go, then
I'm taking your lunchbox.
Why is there suddenly a
staircase leading down?
It's the only way in.
Let's just go with the plug.
Hey, I wonder if these
skeletons can poop too.
Check it out, everyone.
It's Cerberus.
We're literally on the
path to hell right now.
Aw, I think it's kind of cute.
Are they a threat?
Because I'm feeling super.
Three heads are overkill.
Blender with a teeth like.
Weird how they got all
riled up out of nowhere.
Anyway.
Uh-uh. Dips.
I'm going to tame this bad boy.
You idiot, you can't just tame it.
You do know it's not a regular dog, yeah?
How different can it be?
Come on, who's a good boy?
Shake.
I assume we all saw this moment coming.
What big, strong teeth you have.
Now let go of Uncle Luffy's head.
That's a good boy's.
Easy does it, just like I said. No, shit!
Roll over.
That just happened.
The poor thing's body
looks pretty beat up.
I'm surprised it can still
walk around like that.
I wonder what wise-ass put this thing
together, because whoever it was,
they can't tell the difference
between a dog head and a fox head.
If this is the first creature
we met on the island,
I can't wait to see what
other stuff we run into.
Cerberus seems pretty down in the mouth.
Come on, Robin.
Don't pity him.
It just makes him feel worse.
Leave him alone already.
Can you hear me, Nami Sweet?
Hello?
Where are you, my feisty truffle?
I'm all turned around.
It's like a maze full of creepy.
Hey, wait up!
A tree with some geezer's face is totally
getting drunk with a beat-up unicorn!
Look what I got!
Please, just let me go!
They're so cool!
How about you join my pirate crew?
Overruled, dumbass!
That was too close.
You're there, right, Absalom?
I can never tell.
What was all that ruckus?
Were you peeking in on
a bathing beauty again?
I'm on the hunt for a bride, Hogback.
The redhead.
I quite fancy her.
I'll make her mine soon enough.
I hate to burst your bubble, but you
shouldn't go marrying the Golden Goose.
What's that supposed to mean?
We have six guests with bounties
on their heads this time,
including that girl you like.
Her captain's worth 300 million berries.
300 million?
You don't seem very worried, Verona.
If his bounty is that high, we can
only assume he's one tough customer.
If you understand that, then you'll
know you have to go all out on this one.
And that means no chasing skirts.
Looks like we'll have
ourselves a busy night tonight.
Invisible men don't exist, Nami.
End of discussion.
I didn't imagine it, you ninny.
When you came in there, you saw how it
was holding me off the ground, didn't you?
Yeah, I saw.
I mean, uh, sorry, Nami. Didn't
see a thing. Don't lie to me.
Ah, trick question.
That's no fair.
As soon as I confess to seeing
you naked, I'm done for!
You're gonna slap me into next week!
Ah!
I'm not trying to play mind games here!
The slapping can wait!
See? I knew it!
You wanna know what I think?
Nothing I've seen on this island has
been real, including you being naked.
The Invisible Man was just a draft.
The ghosts were weird birds.
And the zombies were just
some underground tribe.
Are you nuts? Sure,
we ran into a fiddle-playing
skeleton with an
afro who was brought back
to life by Devil Fruit,
but he was the exception.
No two devil fruits in
the world work the same.
If his fruit brought him back
to life, then he's the only one.
So zombies and ghosts and all the other
horrible stuff around here is impossible,
right, Chopper?
Huh?
Come on, back me up.
The creatures we saw,
there's no natural explanation
for them, so they can't be real.
If you're looking at this from a medical
point of view, then you're correct, Usopp.
There should be an explanation
for all this stuff.
Then again, if Dr.
Hogback thought his work on the island was
important enough to leave
his whole life behind,
maybe the natural order of things has
turned upside down on this island.
That is not what I wanted to hear.
Maybe Hogback's not the
hero you think he is. Dr.
Hogback is an amazing
man and a medical titan!
I think he's incredible!
How come you think the worst of him?
We don't know if he's
friends with those zombies.
You can't prove anything!
Hey!
All right, let's go ask Dr.
Hogback what he thinks.
How's that sound?
That sounds horrible.
I wish Luffy would hurry up and save us.
I know I don't have anything to base it
on yet, but I don't trust that Hogback.
He gives me the creeps.
Isn't this the room we just ate dinner in?
Yeah, so how come it's pitch
black in here? What the?
Uh, Shandora, you around? Dr.
Hogback, can you hear me?
Yeah, we're done with the bathroom.
I'm afraid the doctor and Shandora
have called it a day. Wait!
Hildon?
Why, you little,
what's the big idea ditching our carriage
in the middle of a scary graveyard?
I feel bad about that.
Out of nowhere, I really
had to go to the bathroom.
You know how it is.
You're such a liar.
Admit it, weirdo.
You're in cahoots with those zombies.
How could you say such awful
things about poor Hildon?
But enough of that unpleasantness.
If you'll follow me to the guest rooms...
So if you don't turn us into Zombie
Chow at first, try, try again?
I don't trust you any farther
than I can throw you, Pudgy.
FYI, we're leaving here right now, and
there's nothing you can do about it.
Huh? Wait a minute!
Just let me trade things out with Dr.
Hogback!
Looks like you bungled it, Hildon.
You don't have to be so mean to me.
I'll take them up to their rooms, okay?
I think it's a little late for that.
These three have noticed
far too much around here.
We can't risk them
telling anyone about us.
I don't believe it!
The painting!
It's holding the conversation
with us like it's people!
You're so cute, I can
swallow you whole right now!
Let go of him!
The painting's trying to eat Chopper!
I want to be a seller!
Get your butt over here and help!
I'm Oral Support!
It is not the painting that you have to
worry about, but I, the Great Orchuk.
You fools will never leave this room alive
again, so just get that out of your head.
That mounted pig head on
the wall is talking too.
And it threw a sword!
I know you're busy, Nami, but there's a
pretty threatening taxidermy back here!
Wait up.
Is that a sword?
Okay, who's the wise guy
who stabbed the bear skin?
Nami was right!
This mansion is wall-to-wall zombies!
Even the decorations!
What are you doing?
Here it comes!
Eat this, you freaky undead frog!
I can't believe you threw a candle at me!
Seriously, who does that?
We've gotta find him!
The guy on the chandelier did it!
Throw the candles in him,
see how much he likes it!
Oh no you don't, because I know your
weakness, foul minions of the underworld!
The power of Usopp compels you!
Nami, Chopper, open the door!
We need to get out of here!
I don't care about Dr. Hogback!
I want to leave!
Open it!
My heart can't take much more of this!
What are you doing, Nami?
You're kidding, right?
No, I'm not!
We're really trapped in here, Usof!
How dare you set me on fire,
you dumb little Pierre!
You're not getting away that easy!
What now?!
That was way too close!
We gotta get to a different room!
Anything beats this!
Not so fast!
No, no, no!
This isn't the way out!
It's just a fireplace!
We're dead!
There's nowhere else to run! Daddy!
Where the heck are we?
Damn it! What happened?
They disappeared all
of a sudden! Not quite.
There's a secret passageway
behind the fireplace.
If we don't catch them,
they're going to make it to Dr.
Hogback's research lab.
It's no good!
They must be blocking
it from the other side!
Run and run wherever
you like, little humans.
You'll find that the mansion is full
of surprise zombies at every turn.
This hallway is bad!
Any place with paintings is bad!
There's gotta be a room in here somewhere!
That's it!
Oh, they're just photos.
No zombies.
Everything's fine.
Hey, wait.
It's that girl from before.
The one who hates plates so much.
Shandora.
It's weird.
What is this room?
Now that I get a better look,
she's really pretty, isn't she?
She sure doesn't look
like a servant, though.
But wait.
You don't think this
place is her room, do you?
That'd be a little odd.
I mean, who would have so many photos
of themselves in their own room?
What about all those
big stitches she's got?
They aren't in any of the photos.
You're right.
And look at that smile.
She's like a completely different
person than the one we met.
Maybe these are old photos
and she had some accident.
I mean, it's got to be her.
Victoria Shandora. Huh?
Evidently, she used to be
a really popular actress.
Take a look.
All these articles are about her.
Huh?
She was an actress?
I thought they said she got into trouble
for breaking a bunch
of plates or something.
So you mean she wasn't
a servant after all?
On the contrary, this says she
came from an aristocratic family.
She had a successful career on the stage.
And even as a child,
she had a lot of fans.
What is it?
These articles are old.
Ten years ago, she fell from the
stage and died in an accident.
That can't be right!
We saw her ourselves!
I mean, she is kind of creepy,
but she's definitely alive!
He's right!
So if what that article
says is true after all,
she must have come back from the dead!
There's no other answer!
All those zombies we saw weren't
some kind of weird monsters!
They were people and animals who had
died and been brought back to life!
I don't like this at all.
I don't even want to
think about it anymore.
Let's just forget we ever
came here and run away.
What now?
Wait a sec.
Is that what I think it is? It is.
It's a treasure chest.
Better already?
Well, what are you waiting for, Usopp?
Open it up, come on!
All right!
Sorry, suckers, but there's
no treasure in this room!
It's a dragon!
There you are!
Hey, zombies!
He said there was no
treasure in that room.
They must be hiding
something somewhere else.
Huh?
It's the bodyguard.
It seems some lost lambs have
wandered into the mansion.
Oh, you're just in time.
But never fear.
I shall herd them up.
For the last time, Luffy,
the skeleton was bad enough.
We don't need trees and
unicorns on the crew.
I mean, look, we've already
got a raccoon dog and a robot.
That's messed up enough.
Hey, how many times do I got to tell you?
I'm not a robot.
I'm a cyborg.
All right, whatever.
Either way, you're not human.
In my heart, I'm a human.
That's what matters.
In your heart, you're a pervert, pal.
Oh, then you understand after all.
No, that was not a compliment.
What kind of monsters are we gonna see?
I hope they join the crew
and come along with me.
There's something I
couldn't help but notice
about that tree man and
the unicorn earlier.
What's that?
Just like our doggy friend here,
all of the creatures in this
forest seem to have heavy injuries.
Big stitches and numbers written on them
somewhere numbers, huh? That's true.
I didn't put much thought into
it myself But are you saying
these things are all working
for someone something like that?
Yes?
Hey guys, you hear those noises?
That's awesome!
Negative, negative, negative.
Kind of annoying how they keep
saying negative over and over.
I'm going to catch it
and keep it as a pick!
Looks like it really is a ghost, huh?
All right.
Red Fire!
Well, damn it.
Guess that didn't work.
I totally suck.
Everything I did this week totally sucks.
Everything I've ever done totally sucks.
I might as well lie down and die.
This should make me into a ceiling fan.
So your attack didn't work!
Don't be a baby!
Okay.
I wouldn't die.
I'd be reincarnated as a clam.
I can't cut it as a human.
I'm useless.
Just leave me here.
Get over it already!
What the hell's wrong with you?
Negative.
Negative, negative.
It would appear that when the
ghosts pass through someone's body,
they become depressed.
And how does that make any sense?
Those two are just straight-up pathetic.
If they had even an ounce
of proper discipline,
they wouldn't let themselves
fall to pieces over
some measly little ghost
barely even touching them.
I'm not even fit to be dog food.
Okay, I get it.
What a pain.
Though it looks like Robin's
theory turned out to be spot on.
None of our attacks can harm them.
But if they pass through our
bodies, we'll be rendered helpless.
They might prove troublesome
if we have to fight them.
No kidding!
What a strange island?
Negative, negative, negative, negative.
You know what?
Screw you, ghost!
I don't want to have you as a pet anymore!
I want to crush you!
Whatever their weak
point is, I'll find it.
Just you wait!
I should call you dog food. Shut up!
The patchwork creatures with the
numbers on them may look frightening,
but they seem easy enough to defeat.
The ghosts, on the other hand,
seem to be exactly the opposite.
There was one of them on the ship earlier.
They show up, then vanish.
Seems to me like they're watching us.
If that's the case, the question
is, who's pulling the strings?
Hey, check it out!
It's a giant graveyard!
Cool!
Perfect place for a picnic,
don't you think? No way!
This atmosphere will ruin the taste!
Hey, don't put me back
on the ground, jackass!
It's an old man with serious injuries.
Are you nuts?
It's a zombie!
Don't make fun of me!
Are zombies usually this... energetic?
I'll show you how dangerous
zombies can really be!
Oh, you guys want to fight, huh?
Then I'll show you how
dangerous pirates can be!
So, what are all you
guys doing out here, huh?
Well, zombie stuff mostly, you know, being
buried, hanging out, rotting and stuff.
Yeah, pretty much rotting and hanging out.
Yep, same here.
You're not lying to me, are you?
No, really, that's the truth, we swear.
Zombie stuff, that's all.
I see.
Then let me ask you something.
Did a man with a long nose,
a woman with orange hair,
and a reindeer that looks like
a raccoon dog come through here?
Oh, yeah, right, right, right.
We may have seen them, but
we're not supposed to...
Sorry, we can't say.
Oilers, oilers, oilers, oilers, oilers.
Oh, I see.
So you're not going to tell me, huh?
I mean, yeah, we saw them.
Those guys are part of my crew Listen up,
you didn't do anything to them, did you?
Wait, they're on your crew?
No, we didn't, right?
Right, we did nothing at all.
I want the truth right now!
This guy did something.
Hey, shut up, Tattletail!
And anyway, you're the one that bit them.
Actually, we all did.
Idiots, shut up!
I saw you fight those zombies.
All of you have such
unbelievable strength.
There's something I'd
like to talk to you about
would you please listen old
man with serious Injuries
idiot we told you they're
zombies oh actually he's
right on the money that's
too Confusing can't you
just be a zombie geez all
right so what did you want
to tell us There's an evil
man who must be brought
down and I think you
youngsters are strong enough
to do it He's left a trail
of victims in his wake.
If you defeat him, they'll all be rescued.
If you'd help me get my shadow
back, I'd be ever so grateful.
Let me take a look.
It's true, see?
He really doesn't have a shadow.
He's just like Brooke.
Well, damn, that sucks.
So who did that to you? Is he here?
Somewhere on this island?
Mor... Moria.
His name is Moria, and he's terrifying.
Moria?
You don't mean...
Gecko Moria by any chance?
That's right.
Yes, that's him.
Robin, do you know this guy?
Yes, but only by name.
And if I remember correctly, his former
bounty was even higher than yours, Luffy.
Wait. Former?
So that means...
Yes.
Gekkomoria is one of the
seven warlords of the sea.